Shubham Kumar

MERN Stack Developer



shubhkmr1806@gmail.com

+917701973670

in shubham-kumar

1shubh

Portfolio

Delhi

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development (Full Time), Masai School ⊗

05/2022 - 12/2022 | Bengaluru, Karnataka

B.Tech (Electronics and instrumentation engineering),

SCRIET, CCS UNIVERSITY Meerut ${\mathscr O}$

08/2013 - 06/2017 | Meerut, Uttar Pradesh

TECHNICAL SKILLS

React.JS • React Native • JavaScript •

HTML • CSS • GitHub • Typescript •

Next.js • Redux • Firebase

SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork • Creativity • Problem-solving

LANGUAGES

- Hindi
- English

INTEREST

Rap ∂

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An enthusiastic and self-driven Full Stack Developer with skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node js Express Js, MongoDB, React.Js, React native and Redux and has over 2 + years of coding experience and has developed multiple fully functional websites and apps for well known firms and has excellent problem-solving skills and the ability to perform well in a team.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer, SLDC Delhi ∂

09/2024 - present | Delhi, India

"Designed and Developed a mobile app for SLDC Delhi using React Native to display real-time data, built the backend in Node.js, and deployed it on local servers like windows IIS."

Frontend Developer Freelancer, Fiverr.com *⊘*

06/2022 - 09/2024

2 years of freelancing experience as a frontend React Js developer, Worked on multiple projects with well known companies of india like Toyota and Maruti Suzuki and has 5 Star Ratings and great feedbacks and reviews from clients on fiverr.com

PROJECTS

1. Property Booking WebApp (Scenic Homes) *⊗*

2024

Github ⊘ Deployed ⊘

"Designed and developed a full-stack property booking web app using React.js and Firebase, allowing users to view, customize, and book properties with options like doors, windows, wall colors, flooring, and faucets. Implemented a role-based login system for users and admins, enabling property and order management features for admins."

Tech Stack:

React JS | Redux | Tailwind CSS | Google Firebase It is an individual project executed in 15 days.

2. Wallmart.com (clone) ∂

Github ⊘ Deployed ⊘

It is an Ecommerce website where a user can buy products from different categories.

Features

- Login and logout.
- Add To cart.
- Checkout page with multiple payment options.

Tech Stack:

ReactJS | Redux | Rest API | Chakra UI
It is an individual project executed in 3 days.